{
  "uniqueId": 38,
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "any of numerous agile ruminants related to sheep but having a beard and straight horns  ",
      "answer": "goat"
    },
    {
      "question": "an insignificant sum of money",
      "answer": "peanuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "the proprietor of a newspaper  ",
      "answer": "publisher"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a steep manner",
      "answer": "steeply"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small metal cap to protect the finger while sewing",
      "answer": "thimble"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman waiter  ",
      "answer": "waitress"
    },
    {
      "question": "wearing boots  ",
      "answer": "booted"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of handwriting, print, etc.) not legible",
      "answer": "illegible"
    },
    {
      "question": "brace consisting of a bar or rod used to resist longitudinal compression  ",
      "answer": "strut"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tapering point  ",
      "answer": "acumen"
    },
    {
      "question": "a very large pot that is used for boiling  ",
      "answer": "caldron"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhibiting biological specialization",
      "answer": "differentiated"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of feeling no fear  ",
      "answer": "fearlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "abounding in small stones",
      "answer": "gravelly"
    },
    {
      "question": "very pleasantly inviting",
      "answer": "tantalizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disposition to be distant and unsympathetic in manner  ",
      "answer": "aloofness"
    },
    {
      "question": "heat by a natural force",
      "answer": "broil"
    },
    {
      "question": "patient endurance especially of pain or distress  ",
      "answer": "sufferance"
    },
    {
      "question": "with taste",
      "answer": "tastefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large mass of ice floating at sea",
      "answer": "iceberg"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who acts as if possessed by a demon  ",
      "answer": "demoniac"
    },
    {
      "question": "ceasing to exist",
      "answer": "disappearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "not politic",
      "answer": "impolitic"
    },
    {
      "question": "lay spawn",
      "answer": "spawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "draw a harrow over (land)  ",
      "answer": "harrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "immaculately clean and unused",
      "answer": "pristine"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act of explaining that serves to clear up and cast light on  ",
      "answer": "elucidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "two words that can be interchanged in a context are said to be synonymous relative to that context  ",
      "answer": "synonym"
    },
    {
      "question": "protective outer layer of seeds of flowering plants  ",
      "answer": "testa"
    },
    {
      "question": "arm in advance of a confrontation  ",
      "answer": "forearm"
    },
    {
      "question": "producing no result or effect",
      "answer": "futile"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who comes to a country where they were not born in order to settle there  ",
      "answer": "immigrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "the keeper of a public house  ",
      "answer": "publican"
    },
    {
      "question": "concern with worldly affairs to the neglect of spiritual needs",
      "answer": "worldliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the business of a butcher  ",
      "answer": "butchery"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hole through which buttons are pushed  ",
      "answer": "buttonhole"
    },
    {
      "question": "enclosed in a case  ",
      "answer": "cased"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inextricable manner",
      "answer": "inextricably"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a play of lustrous rainbow colors",
      "answer": "iridescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the state that someone is in between puberty and adulthood  ",
      "answer": "adolescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "support with evidence or authority or make more certain or confirm",
      "answer": "corroborate"
    },
    {
      "question": "deprived of your rightful heritage  ",
      "answer": "disinherited"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking sensitivity or the capacity for deep feeling  ",
      "answer": "soulless"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of abandoning a party for cause  ",
      "answer": "apostasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill to excess so that function is impaired",
      "answer": "clog"
    },
    {
      "question": "affected with palsy or uncontrollable tremor",
      "answer": "palsied"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of decisions and contracts  ",
      "answer": "indissoluble"
    },
    {
      "question": "a manner of speaking that is natural to native speakers of a language  ",
      "answer": "parlance"
    },
    {
      "question": "set used to broadcast radio or tv signals  ",
      "answer": "transmitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "wasting time  ",
      "answer": "dilatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "impede the movement of (an opponent or a ball)",
      "answer": "parry"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tavern where ale is sold  ",
      "answer": "alehouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with tar or asphalt",
      "answer": "asphalt"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mechanical device consisting of bars at either end of a vehicle to absorb shock and prevent serious damage  ",
      "answer": "bumper"
    },
    {
      "question": "gradually decreasing until little remains  ",
      "answer": "dwindling"
    },
    {
      "question": "not tractable",
      "answer": "intractable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a minor parish official who serves a ceremonial function  ",
      "answer": "beadle"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of demolishing  ",
      "answer": "demolition"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunting ducks  ",
      "answer": "ducking"
    },
    {
      "question": "advance beyond the usual limit  ",
      "answer": "encroach"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the manner of someone who is very hungry",
      "answer": "hungrily"
    },
    {
      "question": "not permitting extrication",
      "answer": "inextricable"
    },
    {
      "question": "give off a shimmering reflection, as of silk  ",
      "answer": "shimmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "machine tool for shaping metal or wood",
      "answer": "lathe"
    },
    {
      "question": "American hakes  ",
      "answer": "ling"
    },
    {
      "question": "aromatic acid-tasting pear-shaped fruit used in preserves  ",
      "answer": "quince"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or involving a sacrament  ",
      "answer": "sacramental"
    },
    {
      "question": "powerfully persuasive",
      "answer": "cogent"
    },
    {
      "question": "(poetic) occurring in the dark or night",
      "answer": "darkling"
    },
    {
      "question": "any green goods that are good to eat",
      "answer": "eater"
    },
    {
      "question": "too improbable to admit of belief",
      "answer": "improbable"
    },
    {
      "question": "sad beyond comforting",
      "answer": "inconsolable"
    },
    {
      "question": "running or extending in the direction of the length of a thing",
      "answer": "lengthwise"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or secreting or covered with or resembling mucus",
      "answer": "mucous"
    },
    {
      "question": "(economics) the ratio of the quantity and quality of units produced to the labor per unit of time  ",
      "answer": "productivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "shield consisting of an arrangement of metal mesh or plates designed to protect electronic equipment from ambient electromagnetic interference  ",
      "answer": "shielding"
    },
    {
      "question": "attempting to justify or defend in speech or writing  ",
      "answer": "defensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a jaunty fashionable manner",
      "answer": "jauntily"
    },
    {
      "question": "having pillars",
      "answer": "pillared"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or denoting a high range",
      "answer": "soprano"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who maintains and audits business accounts  ",
      "answer": "accountant"
    },
    {
      "question": "compress or concentrate",
      "answer": "condense"
    },
    {
      "question": "an expert in the science of economics  ",
      "answer": "economist"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being bland and gracious or ingratiating in manner  ",
      "answer": "suavity"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a charitable manner",
      "answer": "charitably"
    },
    {
      "question": "analyze (chemical substances)  ",
      "answer": "assay"
    },
    {
      "question": "a chronic emphysema of the horse that causes difficult expiration and heaving of the flanks  ",
      "answer": "heaves"
    },
    {
      "question": "the feeling you have when you have hope  ",
      "answer": "hopefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "handgrip formed by the raised front part of a saddle  ",
      "answer": "pommel"
    },
    {
      "question": "adapted to social or economic change",
      "answer": "reconstructed"
    },
    {
      "question": "sticking out",
      "answer": "obtrusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a university student who has not yet received a first degree  ",
      "answer": "undergraduate"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepare (students) hastily for an impending exam  ",
      "answer": "cram"
    },
    {
      "question": "large Australian flightless bird similar to the ostrich but smaller  ",
      "answer": "emu"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman entrusted with the care and supervision of a child (especially in a private home)  ",
      "answer": "governess"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an irretrievable manner",
      "answer": "irretrievably"
    },
    {
      "question": "rolled up and secured",
      "answer": "furled"
    },
    {
      "question": "drive (a team of dogs or a dogsled)  ",
      "answer": "mush"
    },
    {
      "question": "an entrenched stronghold or refuge  ",
      "answer": "redoubt"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by changeable fortune",
      "answer": "checkered"
    },
    {
      "question": "toward or in the lower or central part of town  ",
      "answer": "downtown"
    },
    {
      "question": "extricate from entanglement",
      "answer": "disentangle"
    },
    {
      "question": "spear with a harpoon",
      "answer": "harpoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "of girls or women who are eligible to marry  ",
      "answer": "marriageable"
    },
    {
      "question": "failure of a plan  ",
      "answer": "miscarriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "take something as preexisting and given  ",
      "answer": "premise"
    },
    {
      "question": "experiencing or expressing gladness or joy",
      "answer": "gladsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "a heavy rain  ",
      "answer": "downpour"
    },
    {
      "question": "be extremely bad in quality or in one's performance",
      "answer": "stink"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a nice way",
      "answer": "nicely"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking power  ",
      "answer": "powerless"
    },
    {
      "question": "not cleaned with or as if with soap and water",
      "answer": "unwashed"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to move faster",
      "answer": "accelerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being kind and gentle  ",
      "answer": "benignity"
    },
    {
      "question": "(medicine) someone who gives blood or tissue or an organ to be used in another person (the host)  ",
      "answer": "donor"
    },
    {
      "question": "made slick by e.g. ice or grease",
      "answer": "slick"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffered or done by one person as a substitute for another",
      "answer": "vicarious"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of lacking general approval or acceptance  ",
      "answer": "unpopularity"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) an affidavit attached to a statement confirming the truth of that statement  ",
      "answer": "verification"
    },
    {
      "question": "payment of a debt or obligation  ",
      "answer": "repayment"
    },
    {
      "question": "container for coal",
      "answer": "scuttle"
    },
    {
      "question": "your friends and acquaintances",
      "answer": "kith"
    },
    {
      "question": "tough elastic tissue",
      "answer": "cartilage"
    },
    {
      "question": "a little bit at a time",
      "answer": "piecemeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the infliction of extremely painful punishment or suffering  ",
      "answer": "crucifixion"
    },
    {
      "question": "an exclamation of protest or remonstrance or reproof  ",
      "answer": "expostulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "standing or position on a scale  ",
      "answer": "rating"
    },
    {
      "question": "advocating or following the socialist principles",
      "answer": "socialistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "coat with stucco",
      "answer": "stucco"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physiology) moving of a body part away from the central axis of the body  ",
      "answer": "abduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing the wearing effects of overwork or care or suffering",
      "answer": "careworn"
    },
    {
      "question": "adult male swan  ",
      "answer": "cob"
    },
    {
      "question": "eating to excess (personified as one of the deadly sins)  ",
      "answer": "gluttony"
    },
    {
      "question": "make sick or ill",
      "answer": "sicken"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a typical manner",
      "answer": "typically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a diacritical mark (U-shaped) placed over a vowel to indicate a short sound  ",
      "answer": "breve"
    },
    {
      "question": "the power to foresee the future  ",
      "answer": "prescience"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling a pyramid  ",
      "answer": "pyramidal"
    },
    {
      "question": "an animal especially a mammal having four limbs specialized for walking  ",
      "answer": "quadruped"
    },
    {
      "question": "coarse fabric used for bags or sacks  ",
      "answer": "sacking"
    },
    {
      "question": "not restricted or modified in meaning",
      "answer": "unrestricted"
    },
    {
      "question": "preventing entry or exit or a course of action",
      "answer": "barricaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "cylindrical green fruit with thin green rind and white flesh eaten as a vegetable",
      "answer": "cucumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being united into one  ",
      "answer": "oneness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being usable  ",
      "answer": "practicability"
    },
    {
      "question": "rub soap all over, usually with the purpose of cleaning  ",
      "answer": "soap"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or arising from a benefice",
      "answer": "beneficiary"
    },
    {
      "question": "one of a pair of heavy flat disk-shaped stones that are rotated against one another to grind the grain  ",
      "answer": "millstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of actually existing objectively",
      "answer": "actuality"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a region of the United States generally including Washington",
      "answer": "northwestern"
    },
    {
      "question": "greatness of magnitude  ",
      "answer": "amplitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "be exposed",
      "answer": "bask"
    },
    {
      "question": "a riblike part of a plant or animal (such as a middle rib of a leaf or a thickened vein of an insect wing)  ",
      "answer": "costa"
    },
    {
      "question": "having joints or jointed segments",
      "answer": "jointed"
    },
    {
      "question": "run faster than",
      "answer": "outrun"
    },
    {
      "question": "action that makes a problem or a disease (or its symptoms) worse",
      "answer": "aggravation"
    },
    {
      "question": "sing carols",
      "answer": "carol"
    },
    {
      "question": "set afire",
      "answer": "ignited"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a clank",
      "answer": "clank"
    },
    {
      "question": "form a circle around",
      "answer": "encircle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a metallic element having four allotropic forms",
      "answer": "antimony"
    },
    {
      "question": "medieval body armor that covers the chest and back  ",
      "answer": "cuirass"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a pale to moderate greyish violet color  ",
      "answer": "mauve"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of concentrating on one central objective",
      "answer": "singleness"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several low composite herbs of the genera Artemisia or Seriphidium  ",
      "answer": "wormwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "the type of environment in which an organism or group normally lives or occurs",
      "answer": "habitat"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a smudge on",
      "answer": "smear"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a startling manner",
      "answer": "startlingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "conveying information to the muscles from the CNS",
      "answer": "centrifugal"
    },
    {
      "question": "general acceptance or use",
      "answer": "currency"
    },
    {
      "question": "draw back, as with fear or pain",
      "answer": "flinch"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who collects things that have been discarded by others  ",
      "answer": "magpie"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of meeting financial obligations  ",
      "answer": "solvent"
    },
    {
      "question": "produced by the action of water  ",
      "answer": "aqueous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a chest especially for storing valuables  ",
      "answer": "coffer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a concise reference book providing specific information about a subject or location  ",
      "answer": "handbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "wetness in the atmosphere  ",
      "answer": "humidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "detach the affections of  ",
      "answer": "wean"
    },
    {
      "question": "deep-sea fish with a large head and body and long tapering tail  ",
      "answer": "grenadier"
    },
    {
      "question": "any thallophytic plant of the division Lichenes",
      "answer": "lichen"
    },
    {
      "question": "descent of the uterus into the pelvic cavity that occurs late in pregnancy",
      "answer": "lightening"
    },
    {
      "question": "used to refer to cited works  ",
      "answer": "passim"
    },
    {
      "question": "raise trivial objections  ",
      "answer": "cavil"
    },
    {
      "question": "logical and orderly and consistent relation of parts  ",
      "answer": "coherence"
    },
    {
      "question": "either of two folds of skin that can be moved to cover or open the eye",
      "answer": "eyelid"
    },
    {
      "question": "elegant and stylish",
      "answer": "chic"
    },
    {
      "question": "sewing consisting of pieces of different materials sewn together in a pattern  ",
      "answer": "patchwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "write a script for",
      "answer": "script"
    },
    {
      "question": "obviously contrived to charm",
      "answer": "cute"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of swindling by some fraudulent scheme",
      "answer": "swindle"
    },
    {
      "question": "complain",
      "answer": "gripe"
    },
    {
      "question": "refined sensitivity to pleasurable or painful impressions",
      "answer": "sensibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "a group of men who escort and protect some important person  ",
      "answer": "bodyguard"
    },
    {
      "question": "serving to set in motion",
      "answer": "inaugural"
    },
    {
      "question": "make the chemically affected part of (a negative) denser or more opaque in order produce a stronger contrast between light and dark  ",
      "answer": "intensify"
    },
    {
      "question": "the occupation of taking and printing photographs or making movies  ",
      "answer": "photography"
    },
    {
      "question": "exalted to an ideal perfection or excellence  ",
      "answer": "idealized"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the state of marriage",
      "answer": "marital"
    },
    {
      "question": "a machine for sorting things (such as punched cards or letters) into classes  ",
      "answer": "sorter"
    },
    {
      "question": "hostile or indifferent to religion  ",
      "answer": "irreligious"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several trees of the genus Populus having leaves on flattened stalks so that they flutter in the lightest wind  ",
      "answer": "aspen"
    },
    {
      "question": "one having charge of buildings or grounds or animals  ",
      "answer": "custodian"
    },
    {
      "question": "close or secure with or as if with a stopper",
      "answer": "stopper"
    },
    {
      "question": "changing to a lighter color  ",
      "answer": "whitening"
    },
    {
      "question": "an assistant to a bishop  ",
      "answer": "coadjutor"
    },
    {
      "question": "surgically remove (an organ)  ",
      "answer": "extirpate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large commercial ship (especially one that carries passengers on a regular schedule)  ",
      "answer": "liner"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the buttocks  ",
      "answer": "natal"
    },
    {
      "question": "starchy banana-like fruit",
      "answer": "plantain"
    },
    {
      "question": "prescribed or authorized by or punishable under a statute",
      "answer": "statutory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a receptacle where waste can be discarded",
      "answer": "garbage"
    },
    {
      "question": "not evidencing any purpose or goal  ",
      "answer": "purposeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking or characterized by lack of ambition or initiative",
      "answer": "shiftless"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or resembling or typical of a college or college students",
      "answer": "collegiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small pocketknife",
      "answer": "penknife"
    },
    {
      "question": "having accumulated rust",
      "answer": "rusted"
    },
    {
      "question": "one behind the other",
      "answer": "tandem"
    },
    {
      "question": "a printmaker who prints from an engraved printing plate  ",
      "answer": "engraver"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dental appliance that holds teeth (or a prosthesis) in position after orthodontic treatment  ",
      "answer": "retainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "esteem lightly  ",
      "answer": "undervalue"
    },
    {
      "question": "being of questionable authenticity  ",
      "answer": "apocryphal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the final resolution of the main complication of a literary or dramatic work  ",
      "answer": "denouement"
    },
    {
      "question": "a form of baptism in which part or all of a person's body is submerged  ",
      "answer": "immersion"
    },
    {
      "question": "the husband of your mother by a subsequent marriage  ",
      "answer": "stepfather"
    },
    {
      "question": "treated with contempt",
      "answer": "desecrated"
    },
    {
      "question": "meat (especially beef) cut in strips and dried in the sun  ",
      "answer": "jerky"
    },
    {
      "question": "get the better of",
      "answer": "outdo"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or infected by rabies  ",
      "answer": "rabid"
    },
    {
      "question": "deserving regret",
      "answer": "regrettable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person whose occupation is making and altering garments  ",
      "answer": "tailor"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from admixture",
      "answer": "unalloyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "diminished or moderated",
      "answer": "bated"
    },
    {
      "question": "round red root vegetable  ",
      "answer": "beet"
    },
    {
      "question": "swell out or bulge out  ",
      "answer": "belly"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of animals that move seasonally",
      "answer": "migratory"
    },
    {
      "question": "the doctrine of an absolute being  ",
      "answer": "absolutism"
    },
    {
      "question": "the combination of two or more commercial companies  ",
      "answer": "amalgamation"
    },
    {
      "question": "ingestion of liquid food with a spoon or by drinking  ",
      "answer": "supping"
    },
    {
      "question": "not officially established",
      "answer": "unofficial"
    },
    {
      "question": "impervious to pleas, persuasion, requests, reason",
      "answer": "adamant"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to cats",
      "answer": "feline"
    },
    {
      "question": "make into a raft",
      "answer": "raft"
    },
    {
      "question": "collect discarded or refused material",
      "answer": "salvage"
    },
    {
      "question": "large mostly Old World wading birds typically having white-and-black plumage  ",
      "answer": "stork"
    },
    {
      "question": "indulge (one's appetite) to satiety  ",
      "answer": "surfeit"
    },
    {
      "question": "not composed of measured syllables",
      "answer": "unmeasured"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small rectangular block used in playing the game of dominoes",
      "answer": "domino"
    },
    {
      "question": "a celebrity who is an inspiration to others",
      "answer": "luminary"
    },
    {
      "question": "cooked too long but still edible  ",
      "answer": "overdone"
    },
    {
      "question": "having rays or ray-like parts as in the flower heads of daisies  ",
      "answer": "radiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "give a spurt of fuel to",
      "answer": "goose"
    },
    {
      "question": "a side-by-side position  ",
      "answer": "juxtaposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "as if striking with slashing blows",
      "answer": "slashing"
    },
    {
      "question": "an incrustation that forms on the teeth and gums  ",
      "answer": "tartar"
    },
    {
      "question": "an impulsive scatterbrained manner  ",
      "answer": "giddiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter the characteristic sound of owls  ",
      "answer": "hoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of a large group of nitrogenous organic compounds that are essential constituents of living cells",
      "answer": "protein"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by lively action",
      "answer": "bouncing"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling an oracle in obscurity of thought",
      "answer": "enigmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small hole in a fortified wall",
      "answer": "loophole"
    },
    {
      "question": "a contagious disease characterized by purulent skin eruptions that may leave pock marks  ",
      "answer": "pox"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to rent",
      "answer": "rental"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of plants as well as animals) feeding on animals",
      "answer": "carnivorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or showing profound knowledge",
      "answer": "erudite"
    },
    {
      "question": "a summons that commands the appearance of a party at a proceeding  ",
      "answer": "citation"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing seeds of later development",
      "answer": "germinal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a narrative telling the adventures of a hero or a family",
      "answer": "saga"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several large humped bovids having shaggy manes and large heads and short horns  ",
      "answer": "bison"
    },
    {
      "question": "an infection of the intestines marked by severe diarrhea  ",
      "answer": "dysentery"
    },
    {
      "question": "100 fen equal 1 yuan in China  ",
      "answer": "fen"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of numerous perennial bulbous herbs having linear or broadly lanceolate leaves and usually a single showy flower  ",
      "answer": "tulip"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of singing a quiet song to lull a child to sleep  ",
      "answer": "lullaby"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling a reed in being upright and slender  ",
      "answer": "reedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "without defense",
      "answer": "defenseless"
    },
    {
      "question": "grow worse",
      "answer": "devolve"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state or quality of being lodged or fixed even temporarily",
      "answer": "lodgment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of disorder involving group violence  ",
      "answer": "rioting"
    },
    {
      "question": "coil in which voltage is induced by motion through a magnetic field  ",
      "answer": "armature"
    },
    {
      "question": "the county courts of England (replaced in 1971 by Crown courts)  ",
      "answer": "assizes"
    },
    {
      "question": "arranged in a sequence of grades or ranks",
      "answer": "graded"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lucid state of mind",
      "answer": "lucidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "separating the notes",
      "answer": "staccato"
    },
    {
      "question": "deposited or arranged in horizontal layers",
      "answer": "stratified"
    },
    {
      "question": "beyond doubt or reproach",
      "answer": "unimpeachable"
    },
    {
      "question": "an arrangement of parts or elements",
      "answer": "configuration"
    },
    {
      "question": "the government of the Roman Catholic Church  ",
      "answer": "papacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or near the abdomen",
      "answer": "abdominal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a former copper coin of Pakistan and India  ",
      "answer": "anna"
    },
    {
      "question": "a group or class of persons enjoying superior intellectual or social or economic status  ",
      "answer": "elite"
    },
    {
      "question": "the articulation of speech regarded from the point of view of its intelligibility to the audience  ",
      "answer": "enunciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who intervenes with authorities for a person in trouble (usually using underhand or illegal methods for a fee)  ",
      "answer": "fixer"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a daily cycle or occurring every day",
      "answer": "diurnal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female sorcerer or magician  ",
      "answer": "enchantress"
    },
    {
      "question": "small swift graceful antelope of Africa and Asia having lustrous eyes  ",
      "answer": "gazelle"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or involving the stomach",
      "answer": "gastric"
    },
    {
      "question": "rebuking a person harshly  ",
      "answer": "chiding"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a manner or to a degree that could not be doubted",
      "answer": "indubitably"
    },
    {
      "question": "impossible to remedy or correct or redress",
      "answer": "irremediable"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut with a blade or mower",
      "answer": "mow"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tray or stand for writing implements and containers for ink  ",
      "answer": "inkstand"
    },
    {
      "question": "having inner resources",
      "answer": "resourceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "(folklore) a corpse that rises at night to drink the blood of the living  ",
      "answer": "vampire"
    },
    {
      "question": "prop up with a pillow or bolster  ",
      "answer": "bolster"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or composed for an orchestra",
      "answer": "orchestral"
    },
    {
      "question": "dark green leaves",
      "answer": "spinach"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is morally reprehensible",
      "answer": "cad"
    },
    {
      "question": "out of a sense of duty",
      "answer": "dutifully"
    },
    {
      "question": "win easily",
      "answer": "romp"
    },
    {
      "question": "lighted only by stars",
      "answer": "starlit"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to congress",
      "answer": "congressional"
    },
    {
      "question": "stab with a poniard  ",
      "answer": "poniard"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ancestor in the direct line  ",
      "answer": "progenitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "a homeless child especially one forsaken or orphaned",
      "answer": "waif"
    },
    {
      "question": "constituting a disadvantage  ",
      "answer": "disadvantageous"
    },
    {
      "question": "an expert manner of speaking involving control of voice and gesture  ",
      "answer": "elocution"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a wicked and shameful manner",
      "answer": "foully"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of giving pleasure",
      "answer": "pleasantness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman poet  ",
      "answer": "poetess"
    },
    {
      "question": "arachnid of warm dry regions having a long segmented tail ending in a venomous stinger  ",
      "answer": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of movements) light and confidently active",
      "answer": "springy"
    },
    {
      "question": "burn superficially or lightly",
      "answer": "singe"
    },
    {
      "question": "consisting of segments held together by joints  ",
      "answer": "articulated"
    },
    {
      "question": "belittle",
      "answer": "deprecate"
    },
    {
      "question": "any age prior to the legal age  ",
      "answer": "minority"
    },
    {
      "question": "the grouping of musical phrases in a melodic line  ",
      "answer": "phrasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who imports or exports without paying duties  ",
      "answer": "smuggler"
    },
    {
      "question": "laugh nervously",
      "answer": "giggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of eating lunch  ",
      "answer": "lunching"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter indistinctly  ",
      "answer": "slur"
    },
    {
      "question": "a consistency of low viscosity",
      "answer": "thinness"
    },
    {
      "question": "sign as evidence of legal transfer",
      "answer": "endorse"
    },
    {
      "question": "the 13th letter of the Hebrew alphabet  ",
      "answer": "mem"
    },
    {
      "question": "pertaining to or producing electric current by chemical action",
      "answer": "voltaic"
    },
    {
      "question": "back and sides of a hog salted and dried or smoked",
      "answer": "bacon"
    },
    {
      "question": "young bird especially of domestic fowl  ",
      "answer": "chick"
    },
    {
      "question": "move without being stable, as if threatening to fall",
      "answer": "totter"
    },
    {
      "question": "not fully prepared  ",
      "answer": "unripe"
    },
    {
      "question": "within the realm of possibility",
      "answer": "conceivably"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing unfeeling resistance to tender feelings",
      "answer": "flinty"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to promote or preserve health",
      "answer": "hygienic"
    },
    {
      "question": "eat intermittently",
      "answer": "nibble"
    },
    {
      "question": "to an extravagant or immoderate degree",
      "answer": "outrageously"
    },
    {
      "question": "completely acceptable",
      "answer": "unexceptionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to stonemasons or masonry",
      "answer": "masonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a statement that is added to or revises or improves a proposal or document (a bill or constitution etc.)  ",
      "answer": "amendment"
    },
    {
      "question": "fruit of the oak tree: a smooth thin-walled nut in a woody cup-shaped base  ",
      "answer": "acorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "promote somebody by brevet, in the military  ",
      "answer": "brevet"
    },
    {
      "question": "the wife of a duke or a woman holding ducal title in her own right  ",
      "answer": "duchess"
    },
    {
      "question": "the lowermost sail on the mainmast  ",
      "answer": "mainsail"
    },
    {
      "question": "either one of the two external openings to the nasal cavity in the nose  ",
      "answer": "nostril"
    },
    {
      "question": "(British usage) kerosine  ",
      "answer": "paraffin"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhibiting spectral colors formed by refraction of light through a prism",
      "answer": "prismatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "one of a number of uniform projections on a gear  ",
      "answer": "tooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "a seal on a letter  ",
      "answer": "cachet"
    },
    {
      "question": "work together in harmony  ",
      "answer": "mesh"
    },
    {
      "question": "opening in the rear of the barrel of a gun where bullets can be loaded  ",
      "answer": "breech"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of causing disorder  ",
      "answer": "disruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stupid person",
      "answer": "dunce"
    },
    {
      "question": "not produced by natural forces",
      "answer": "factitious"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter with a gurgling sound",
      "answer": "gurgle"
    },
    {
      "question": "by means of language",
      "answer": "verbally"
    },
    {
      "question": "throw a steer by seizing the horns and twisting the neck, as in a rodeo  ",
      "answer": "bulldog"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by anger",
      "answer": "choleric"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a disagreeable manner",
      "answer": "disagreeably"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a grudging manner",
      "answer": "grudgingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "make simpler or easier or reduce in complexity or extent",
      "answer": "simplify"
    },
    {
      "question": "deserving to be admitted",
      "answer": "admissible"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman who cohabits with an important man  ",
      "answer": "concubine"
    },
    {
      "question": "having your composure disturbed",
      "answer": "discomposed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dissenting clique  ",
      "answer": "faction"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fabric used for suits  ",
      "answer": "suiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "attach or become attached to a stem word",
      "answer": "affix"
    },
    {
      "question": "be heavier than  ",
      "answer": "outweigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "concise and full of meaning",
      "answer": "pithy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of trimming a plant  ",
      "answer": "pruning"
    },
    {
      "question": "large drinking vessel with one handle  ",
      "answer": "tankard"
    },
    {
      "question": "the personal outfit of a bride",
      "answer": "trousseau"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who swindles you by means of deception or fraud  ",
      "answer": "swindler"
    },
    {
      "question": "constituting a tube",
      "answer": "tubular"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an appealing manner",
      "answer": "appealingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or characteristic of a dictator",
      "answer": "dictatorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "a reeling sensation",
      "answer": "dizziness"
    },
    {
      "question": "situated at the farthest possible point from a center  ",
      "answer": "outermost"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a tragic manner",
      "answer": "tragically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a piece of armor plate (with eye slits) fixed or hinged to a medieval helmet to protect the face  ",
      "answer": "visor"
    },
    {
      "question": "like the light sharp ringing sound of glasses being tapped  ",
      "answer": "clinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "having spots or patches of color  ",
      "answer": "dappled"
    },
    {
      "question": "money granted (by a university or foundation or other agency) for advanced study or research  ",
      "answer": "fellowship"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being so overabundant that prices fall  ",
      "answer": "glut"
    },
    {
      "question": "exonerate by means of a perfunctory investigation or through biased presentation of data  ",
      "answer": "whitewash"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ancient unit of length based on the length of the forearm  ",
      "answer": "cubit"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an indelible manner",
      "answer": "indelibly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a rhythmic group of eight lines of verse  ",
      "answer": "octave"
    },
    {
      "question": "optical device having a triangular shape and made of glass or quartz",
      "answer": "prism"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Middle Ages) an attendant and shield bearer to a knight",
      "answer": "esquire"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by harshly abusive criticism",
      "answer": "scathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the basic unit of money in Ecuador",
      "answer": "sucre"
    },
    {
      "question": "without official authorization",
      "answer": "unauthorized"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the way and hindering progress",
      "answer": "underfoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to heraldry or heraldic arms",
      "answer": "armorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "a passage with access only at one end  ",
      "answer": "cul"
    },
    {
      "question": "the beneficiary of a pension fund  ",
      "answer": "pensioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut drastically",
      "answer": "slash"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who torments  ",
      "answer": "tormentor"
    },
    {
      "question": "confined to and understandable by only an enlightened inner circle",
      "answer": "esoteric"
    },
    {
      "question": "a laminated metamorphic rock similar to granite  ",
      "answer": "gneiss"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to heraldry  ",
      "answer": "heraldic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an indecent or improper act  ",
      "answer": "indecency"
    },
    {
      "question": "organized again",
      "answer": "reorganized"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sturdy manner",
      "answer": "sturdily"
    },
    {
      "question": "a coming into being  ",
      "answer": "genesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "without rigidity",
      "answer": "limply"
    },
    {
      "question": "expecting the worst possible outcome  ",
      "answer": "pessimistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the innermost light-sensitive membrane covering the back wall of the eyeball",
      "answer": "retina"
    },
    {
      "question": "bound fast especially having the arms restrained  ",
      "answer": "pinioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "blow hard",
      "answer": "bluster"
    },
    {
      "question": "an exciting and mysterious quality (as of a heroic time or adventure)  ",
      "answer": "romanticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "wearing a blindfold  ",
      "answer": "blindfold"
    },
    {
      "question": "(parliamentary procedure) someone who makes a formal motion  ",
      "answer": "proposer"
    },
    {
      "question": "arising from or characterized by prudence especially in business matters",
      "answer": "prudential"
    },
    {
      "question": "the peak of a hill",
      "answer": "hilltop"
    },
    {
      "question": "a strange attitude or habit  ",
      "answer": "oddity"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover by spraying with a liquid",
      "answer": "spray"
    },
    {
      "question": "the basic unit of money in Japan",
      "answer": "yen"
    },
    {
      "question": "small rough-haired breed of terrier from Scotland  ",
      "answer": "cairn"
    },
    {
      "question": "turn red or redder",
      "answer": "redden"
    },
    {
      "question": "become scorched or singed under intense heat or dry conditions",
      "answer": "scorch"
    },
    {
      "question": "a prejudiced person who is intolerant of any opinions differing from his own  ",
      "answer": "bigot"
    },
    {
      "question": "an area adjacent to farm buildings  ",
      "answer": "farmyard"
    },
    {
      "question": "material applied to the outside of a building to make it weatherproof  ",
      "answer": "siding"
    },
    {
      "question": "speak of in an irreverent or impious manner",
      "answer": "blaspheme"
    },
    {
      "question": "be agitated",
      "answer": "churn"
    },
    {
      "question": "lingerie consisting of a loose dress designed to be worn in bed by women  ",
      "answer": "nightgown"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an indiscriminate manner",
      "answer": "promiscuously"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking significance or liveliness or spirit or zest",
      "answer": "vapid"
    },
    {
      "question": "shortening something by omitting parts of it  ",
      "answer": "abbreviation"
    },
    {
      "question": "providing privacy or seclusion",
      "answer": "cloistered"
    },
    {
      "question": "lens used to concentrate light on an object  ",
      "answer": "condenser"
    },
    {
      "question": "(formerly) a cavalryman armed with a lance  ",
      "answer": "lancer"
    },
    {
      "question": "able to take in large quantities of moisture",
      "answer": "thirsty"
    },
    {
      "question": "squeeze or press together",
      "answer": "compress"
    },
    {
      "question": "narrow-minded about cherished opinions  ",
      "answer": "illiberal"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an intuitive manner",
      "answer": "intuitively"
    },
    {
      "question": "plot upon a graph  ",
      "answer": "graph"
    },
    {
      "question": "woodlands in full leaf",
      "answer": "greenwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "separate (experiences) from the emotions relating to them  ",
      "answer": "isolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a maker of laws",
      "answer": "lawgiver"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerned with topography",
      "answer": "topographical"
    },
    {
      "question": "female sheep  ",
      "answer": "ewe"
    },
    {
      "question": "fasten with a bight  ",
      "answer": "bight"
    },
    {
      "question": "abounding in or given to pompous or aphoristic moralizing",
      "answer": "sententious"
    },
    {
      "question": "engaging in or ready for combat  ",
      "answer": "combatant"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who dives (into water)  ",
      "answer": "diver"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or resembling repeated square indentations like those in a battlement",
      "answer": "embattled"
    },
    {
      "question": "the systematic use of spies to get military or political secrets  ",
      "answer": "espionage"
    },
    {
      "question": "bird with strong claws and a stiff tail adapted for climbing and a hard chisel-like bill for boring into wood for insects  ",
      "answer": "woodpecker"
    },
    {
      "question": "formed or conceived by the imagination",
      "answer": "fabricated"
    },
    {
      "question": "not inclined to ask questions  ",
      "answer": "unquestioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking order or methodical arrangement or function",
      "answer": "disorganized"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act or expression of criticism and censure",
      "answer": "rebuke"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who lends money at excessive rates of interest  ",
      "answer": "usurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a rite or body of rites prescribed for public worship  ",
      "answer": "liturgy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sponsor who books and stages public entertainments  ",
      "answer": "showman"
    },
    {
      "question": "fine parchment prepared from the skin of a young animal e.g. a calf or lamb  ",
      "answer": "vellum"
    },
    {
      "question": "the campaign of a candidate to be elected  ",
      "answer": "campaigning"
    },
    {
      "question": "done with or working with others for a common purpose or benefit",
      "answer": "cooperative"
    },
    {
      "question": "artfully persuasive in speech",
      "answer": "glib"
    },
    {
      "question": "not embarrassed",
      "answer": "unabashed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the official act of consigning a person to confinement (as in a prison or mental hospital)  ",
      "answer": "commitment"
    },
    {
      "question": "the study and classification of human societies  ",
      "answer": "sociology"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of subverting",
      "answer": "subversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ornamental flower garden",
      "answer": "parterre"
    },
    {
      "question": "casual or ephemeral as if taking place on board a ship",
      "answer": "shipboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "sharpen by rubbing, as on a whetstone  ",
      "answer": "whet"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by foolish or unreasoning fondness",
      "answer": "enamored"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of persons or behavior",
      "answer": "inclement"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being painstaking and careful  ",
      "answer": "conscientiousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "build (a road) from logs laid side by side  ",
      "answer": "corduroy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nonmetallic element belonging to the halogens",
      "answer": "iodine"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a considerate manner",
      "answer": "considerately"
    },
    {
      "question": "without a flaw",
      "answer": "flawless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a narrow gorge with a stream running through it  ",
      "answer": "gulch"
    },
    {
      "question": "not buried  ",
      "answer": "unburied"
    },
    {
      "question": "without giving a name",
      "answer": "anonymously"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act of appearing or becoming visible unexpectedly",
      "answer": "apparition"
    },
    {
      "question": "endow with a benefice  ",
      "answer": "benefice"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sport that involves exercises intended to display strength and balance and agility  ",
      "answer": "gymnastics"
    },
    {
      "question": "kill a large number of people indiscriminately",
      "answer": "massacre"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a marriage partner  ",
      "answer": "mated"
    },
    {
      "question": "(pathology) causing no symptoms",
      "answer": "quiescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "bearing or marked with a label or tag",
      "answer": "labeled"
    },
    {
      "question": "structure consisting of the part of a ship above the main deck  ",
      "answer": "superstructure"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an irritable manner",
      "answer": "irritably"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sign posted in a public place as an advertisement",
      "answer": "poster"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing or of the nature of alcohol",
      "answer": "spirituous"
    },
    {
      "question": "north temperate shrubs or trees having toothed leaves and conelike fruit",
      "answer": "alder"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who guards an entrance  ",
      "answer": "doorkeeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "massive thick-skinned herbivorous animal living in or around rivers of tropical Africa  ",
      "answer": "hippopotamus"
    },
    {
      "question": "the official announcement of a new law or ordinance whereby the law or ordinance is put into effect  ",
      "answer": "promulgation"
    },
    {
      "question": "destroy completely",
      "answer": "subvert"
    },
    {
      "question": "(British informal) summarized or abridged",
      "answer": "potted"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being worthy of desiring  ",
      "answer": "desirability"
    },
    {
      "question": "a personal attendant of the British royal family  ",
      "answer": "equerry"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Old Testament) large basin used by a priest in an ancient Jewish temple to perform ritual ablutions  ",
      "answer": "laver"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an aggressive manner",
      "answer": "offensively"
    },
    {
      "question": "exonerate by means of an alibi  ",
      "answer": "alibi"
    },
    {
      "question": "become smaller or lose substance",
      "answer": "dwindle"
    },
    {
      "question": "cotton or linen fabric with the nap raised on one side",
      "answer": "lint"
    },
    {
      "question": "a book regarded as authoritative in its field  ",
      "answer": "bible"
    },
    {
      "question": "colloquial American term for a town",
      "answer": "burg"
    },
    {
      "question": "a common nonmetallic element belonging to the halogens",
      "answer": "chlorine"
    },
    {
      "question": "the most typical example or representative of a type  ",
      "answer": "quintessence"
    },
    {
      "question": "having corresponding sounds especially terminal sounds",
      "answer": "rhymed"
    },
    {
      "question": "made without leavening",
      "answer": "unleavened"
    },
    {
      "question": "liquor distilled from fermented molasses  ",
      "answer": "rum"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to animals or animal groups",
      "answer": "zoological"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sorcerer or magician  ",
      "answer": "enchanter"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small sofa  ",
      "answer": "settee"
    },
    {
      "question": "removing by cutting off or clipping  ",
      "answer": "shearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a sad face and thrust out one's lower lip",
      "answer": "pout"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of being conceived or considered  ",
      "answer": "unthinkable"
    },
    {
      "question": "small terrestrial viper common in northern Eurasia  ",
      "answer": "adder"
    },
    {
      "question": "delight greatly in",
      "answer": "wallow"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit lightly",
      "answer": "dab"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of market animals) made ready for market  ",
      "answer": "fattened"
    },
    {
      "question": "the lawyers acting for the state to put the case against the defendant  ",
      "answer": "prosecution"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of adjusting again (to changed circumstances)  ",
      "answer": "readjustment"
    },
    {
      "question": "an informal conversation  ",
      "answer": "chat"
    },
    {
      "question": "decorated metal band worn around the head  ",
      "answer": "circlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who makes copies illegally  ",
      "answer": "forger"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving and relating to the mutual relations of states especially of the United States",
      "answer": "interstate"
    },
    {
      "question": "management that is careless or inefficient",
      "answer": "mismanagement"
    },
    {
      "question": "strangeness as a consequence of being old fashioned",
      "answer": "quaintness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being complete and indiscriminate",
      "answer": "totality"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disorder of the central nervous system characterized by loss of consciousness and convulsions  ",
      "answer": "epilepsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a formal ecclesiastical curse accompanied by excommunication  ",
      "answer": "anathema"
    },
    {
      "question": "congealed into jelly",
      "answer": "congealed"
    },
    {
      "question": "play a game in which players hit a wooden ball through a series of hoops   ",
      "answer": "croquet"
    },
    {
      "question": "the feeling of being intimidated",
      "answer": "intimidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "either of two punctuation marks (or) used to enclose textual material  ",
      "answer": "parenthesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mournful poem",
      "answer": "elegy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a Tibetan or Mongolian priest of Lamaism  ",
      "answer": "lama"
    },
    {
      "question": "(fencing) a second thrust made on the same lunge (as when your opponent fails to riposte)  ",
      "answer": "remise"
    },
    {
      "question": "an aromatic gum resin obtained from various Arabian or East African trees",
      "answer": "frankincense"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a liquid) agitated vigorously",
      "answer": "churning"
    },
    {
      "question": "a skilled worker who practices some trade or handicraft  ",
      "answer": "craftsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "the owner or manager of a brewery  ",
      "answer": "brewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or produced by evolution",
      "answer": "evolutionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "give birth to a litter of animals  ",
      "answer": "litter"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of contributing to the funds of a church or charity",
      "answer": "oblation"
    },
    {
      "question": "having been put right  ",
      "answer": "rectified"
    },
    {
      "question": "misleading by means of pleasant or alluring methods",
      "answer": "beguiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "the main house on a ranch or large estate  ",
      "answer": "hacienda"
    },
    {
      "question": "an indifference to pleasure or pain  ",
      "answer": "stoicism"
    },
    {
      "question": "very drunk  ",
      "answer": "besotted"
    },
    {
      "question": "the syllable naming the fifth (dominant) note of any musical scale in solmization  ",
      "answer": "sol"
    },
    {
      "question": "experiencing intense pain especially mental pain",
      "answer": "anguished"
    },
    {
      "question": "caused to hear poorly or not at all  ",
      "answer": "deafened"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several small tropical Asian lizards capable of gliding by spreading winglike membranes on each side of the body  ",
      "answer": "dragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "presumptuously arrogant",
      "answer": "overweening"
    },
    {
      "question": "a variety show with topical sketches and songs and dancing and comedians  ",
      "answer": "revue"
    },
    {
      "question": "a center of activity or interest or commerce or transportation",
      "answer": "hub"
    },
    {
      "question": "feeling or showing extreme anger",
      "answer": "irate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the residence of a clergyman (especially a Presbyterian clergyman)  ",
      "answer": "manse"
    },
    {
      "question": "partial or total lack of sensation in a part of the body",
      "answer": "numbness"
    },
    {
      "question": "relatively large rodents with sharp erectile bristles mingled with the fur  ",
      "answer": "porcupine"
    },
    {
      "question": "large pure white wild swan of western North America having a sonorous cry  ",
      "answer": "trumpeter"
    },
    {
      "question": "take in nourishment  ",
      "answer": "victual"
    },
    {
      "question": "transport in a wheelbarrow  ",
      "answer": "wheelbarrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending or intended to correct or counteract or restore to a normal condition",
      "answer": "corrective"
    },
    {
      "question": "submerge or plunge suddenly  ",
      "answer": "duck"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ordinal number of forty in counting order  ",
      "answer": "fortieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dense elaborate spider web that is more efficient than the orb web  ",
      "answer": "cobweb"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that agitates and arouses",
      "answer": "excitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a vessel (usually a pot or vat) used for steeping  ",
      "answer": "steeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "come together, usually for a purpose",
      "answer": "congregate"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or serving as an illustration of a type",
      "answer": "emblematic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of contaminating or polluting",
      "answer": "contamination"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a poetic manner",
      "answer": "poetically"
    },
    {
      "question": "American musteline mammal typically ejecting an intensely malodorous fluid when startled",
      "answer": "skunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "fraudulent",
      "answer": "bogus"
    },
    {
      "question": "bring up a topic for discussion  ",
      "answer": "broach"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who uses flattery  ",
      "answer": "flatterer"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered with a dense coat of fine silky hairs",
      "answer": "furred"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone (especially a child) who learns (as from a teacher) or takes up knowledge or beliefs  ",
      "answer": "learner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a habitual or characteristic mental attitude that determines how you will interpret and respond to situations  ",
      "answer": "mentality"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is physically weak and ineffectual  ",
      "answer": "weakling"
    },
    {
      "question": "colloquial British abbreviation",
      "answer": "choc"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of cleaving or splitting  ",
      "answer": "cleavage"
    },
    {
      "question": "gently and sweetly  ",
      "answer": "dolce"
    },
    {
      "question": "rushing about hastily in an undignified way  ",
      "answer": "scamper"
    },
    {
      "question": "lessen, diminish, or curtail",
      "answer": "abridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or involving arithmetic",
      "answer": "arithmetical"
    },
    {
      "question": "(psychology) transfer of a response learned to one stimulus to a similar stimulus  ",
      "answer": "generalization"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who drinks alcoholic beverages (especially to excess)  ",
      "answer": "drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "instructed and encouraged in moral, intellectual, and spiritual improvement  ",
      "answer": "edified"
    },
    {
      "question": "partially melted snow  ",
      "answer": "slush"
    },
    {
      "question": "moisten with fine drops",
      "answer": "drizzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a magistrate",
      "answer": "magisterial"
    },
    {
      "question": "wood that is floating or that has been washed ashore  ",
      "answer": "driftwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "jump about playfully  ",
      "answer": "caper"
    },
    {
      "question": "inability of a part or organ to function properly  ",
      "answer": "incompetence"
    },
    {
      "question": "drawn toward a center or brought under the control of a central authority",
      "answer": "centralized"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of devices and processes) protected by patent",
      "answer": "patented"
    },
    {
      "question": "write carelessly  ",
      "answer": "scribble"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter a high-pitched cry, characteristic of pigs  ",
      "answer": "squeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a card game in which cards face up on the table are taken with eligible cards in the hand  ",
      "answer": "casino"
    },
    {
      "question": "common gregarious Old World bird about the size and color of the American crow  ",
      "answer": "rook"
    },
    {
      "question": "one of a number of large stone statues with the body of a lion and the head of a man that were built by the ancient Egyptians  ",
      "answer": "sphinx"
    },
    {
      "question": "difficult or impossible to extinguish",
      "answer": "inextinguishable"
    },
    {
      "question": "an attractive combination of good health and happiness",
      "answer": "radiance"
    },
    {
      "question": "restore to the previous state or rank  ",
      "answer": "reinstate"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage without restraint in an activity and indulge, as when shopping  ",
      "answer": "spree"
    },
    {
      "question": "all the numbers that end in -teen  ",
      "answer": "teens"
    },
    {
      "question": "associated by chance and not an integral part",
      "answer": "adventitious"
    },
    {
      "question": "an improvement that adds to the value of a property or facility  ",
      "answer": "betterment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a spar projecting from the bow of a vessel  ",
      "answer": "bowsprit"
    },
    {
      "question": "a longing to return home  ",
      "answer": "homesickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a jeweled headdress worn by women on formal occasions  ",
      "answer": "tiara"
    },
    {
      "question": "a statistical relation between two or more variables such that systematic changes in the value of one variable are accompanied by systematic changes in the other  ",
      "answer": "correlation"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a graphic way",
      "answer": "graphically"
    },
    {
      "question": "movement or space for movement",
      "answer": "looseness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a favorite saying of a sect or political group  ",
      "answer": "motto"
    },
    {
      "question": "(logic) an inference that follows directly from the proof of another proposition  ",
      "answer": "corollary"
    },
    {
      "question": "hats for women",
      "answer": "millinery"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who tries to persuade or induce or lead on  ",
      "answer": "persuader"
    },
    {
      "question": "waterproofed canvas  ",
      "answer": "tarpaulin"
    },
    {
      "question": "(architecture) a vaulted structure",
      "answer": "vaulting"
    },
    {
      "question": "a farm implement used to break up the surface of the soil (for aeration and weed control and conservation of moisture)  ",
      "answer": "cultivator"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short passage added at the end of a literary work",
      "answer": "epilogue"
    },
    {
      "question": "not provident",
      "answer": "improvident"
    },
    {
      "question": "unfermented or fermenting malt  ",
      "answer": "wort"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fisherman who uses a hook and line  ",
      "answer": "angler"
    },
    {
      "question": "expressing one thing in terms normally denoting another",
      "answer": "metaphorical"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to find and call attention to faults",
      "answer": "captious"
    },
    {
      "question": "to cause to do through pressure or necessity, by physical, moral or intellectual means :\"She forced him to take a job in the city\"",
      "answer": "coerce"
    },
    {
      "question": "not of a Christian faith  ",
      "answer": "unchristian"
    },
    {
      "question": "without a basis in reason or fact",
      "answer": "baseless"
    },
    {
      "question": "following the teachings or manifesting the qualities or spirit of Jesus Christ  ",
      "answer": "christian"
    },
    {
      "question": "be a part or attribute of  ",
      "answer": "pertain"
    },
    {
      "question": "an anthropoid ape of the genus Proconsul  ",
      "answer": "proconsul"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause an emotional pain, as if by stinging",
      "answer": "sting"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a serial manner",
      "answer": "serially"
    },
    {
      "question": "embellish by sewing in straight lines crossing each other diagonally",
      "answer": "smock"
    },
    {
      "question": "classify or group  ",
      "answer": "bracket"
    },
    {
      "question": "enclose in a capsule  ",
      "answer": "capsule"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sudden outburst (as of protest)  ",
      "answer": "furor"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or associated with or bearing a title signifying nobility",
      "answer": "titular"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or containing basalt",
      "answer": "basaltic"
    },
    {
      "question": "small hardy range horse of the western plains descended from horses brought by the Spanish  ",
      "answer": "mustang"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking love and generosity",
      "answer": "uncharitable"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling or containing bitumen",
      "answer": "bituminous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a linguist who specializes in the study of grammar and syntax  ",
      "answer": "grammarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "loiter about, with no apparent aim  ",
      "answer": "prowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "roll into a ball  ",
      "answer": "clue"
    },
    {
      "question": "a depressing restraint",
      "answer": "damper"
    },
    {
      "question": "familiarize (someone) with new surroundings or circumstances",
      "answer": "orient"
    },
    {
      "question": "the male organ of copulation (`member' is a euphemism)  ",
      "answer": "penis"
    },
    {
      "question": "ruinously destructive and wasting",
      "answer": "ravaging"
    },
    {
      "question": "soak in a special solution to soften and remove chemicals used in previous treatments",
      "answer": "bate"
    },
    {
      "question": "make stronger or defensible",
      "answer": "buttress"
    },
    {
      "question": "a property characteristic of a child  ",
      "answer": "childishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the range within which a voice can be heard",
      "answer": "earshot"
    },
    {
      "question": "a walk of flagstones",
      "answer": "flagging"
    },
    {
      "question": "a performer who juggles objects and performs tricks of manual dexterity  ",
      "answer": "juggler"
    },
    {
      "question": "a preserve made of the pulp and rind of citrus fruits  ",
      "answer": "marmalade"
    },
    {
      "question": "altered in volume as well as tone or pitch  ",
      "answer": "modulated"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various small insectivorous birds of the northern hemisphere that climb up a tree trunk supporting themselves on stiff tail feathers and their feet  ",
      "answer": "creeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inexorable manner",
      "answer": "inexorably"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or containing or caused by mercury",
      "answer": "mercurial"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a radiant manner",
      "answer": "radiantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking help  ",
      "answer": "unassisted"
    },
    {
      "question": "obsolete terms for legal insanity  ",
      "answer": "lunacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "full of seeds",
      "answer": "seedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "not consistent with the methods or principles of science",
      "answer": "unscientific"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act (by someone having the authority) of annulling something previously done",
      "answer": "revocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a quaint and amusing jest  ",
      "answer": "drollery"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of glorifying (as in worship)",
      "answer": "glorification"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a region of the United States generally including New Mexico",
      "answer": "southwestern"
    },
    {
      "question": "surrendered as a penalty  ",
      "answer": "confiscate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of making a strong or vivid impression on the mind  ",
      "answer": "impressiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "running at a jog trot as a form of cardiopulmonary exercise  ",
      "answer": "jogging"
    },
    {
      "question": "a unit of length of thread or yarn  ",
      "answer": "lea"
    },
    {
      "question": "male cat  ",
      "answer": "tom"
    },
    {
      "question": "the staff on which wool or flax is wound before spinning  ",
      "answer": "distaff"
    },
    {
      "question": "a clothing fabric in a plaid weave  ",
      "answer": "gingham"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of linens or clothes) smoothed with a hot iron  ",
      "answer": "ironed"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove with or as if with a ladle",
      "answer": "ladle"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing a sense of shame  ",
      "answer": "shamefaced"
    },
    {
      "question": "a superfluous ornament  ",
      "answer": "embellishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "charge (a public official) with an offense or misdemeanor committed while in office",
      "answer": "impeach"
    },
    {
      "question": "imitating the mannerisms of another person  ",
      "answer": "impersonation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a burial vault (usually for some famous person)  ",
      "answer": "repository"
    },
    {
      "question": "not set afire or burning",
      "answer": "unlighted"
    },
    {
      "question": "on, to, or at the top  ",
      "answer": "atop"
    },
    {
      "question": "a low heavy horse cart without sides",
      "answer": "dray"
    },
    {
      "question": "the position of editor  ",
      "answer": "editorship"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large metal or pottery vessel with a handle and spout",
      "answer": "flagon"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by defiant disregard for danger or consequences",
      "answer": "foolhardy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a quarry worker who splits off blocks of stone  ",
      "answer": "breaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cgs unit of work or energy",
      "answer": "erg"
    },
    {
      "question": "position comfortably",
      "answer": "nestle"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with choice or abundant food or drink",
      "answer": "regale"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nap in the early afternoon (especially in hot countries)  ",
      "answer": "siesta"
    },
    {
      "question": "ask for humbly or earnestly, as in prayer",
      "answer": "supplicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "train on a trellis, as of a vine  ",
      "answer": "trellis"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of applying oil or an oily liquid  ",
      "answer": "anointing"
    },
    {
      "question": "swift-footed terrestrial plover-like bird of southern Asia and Africa",
      "answer": "courser"
    },
    {
      "question": "an award (as for meritorious service) given without claim or obligation  ",
      "answer": "gratuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "difficult to handle or use especially because of size or weight",
      "answer": "cumbersome"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or consisting of or derived from documents  ",
      "answer": "documentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inarticulate manner",
      "answer": "dumbly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the mistake of incurring liability or blame  ",
      "answer": "incursion"
    },
    {
      "question": "conformity with some esthetic standard of correctness or propriety",
      "answer": "justness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a book prepared for use in schools or colleges",
      "answer": "textbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "extravagant self-praise  ",
      "answer": "vaunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "a beef steak usually cooked by broiling  ",
      "answer": "beefsteak"
    },
    {
      "question": "forming or capable of forming or molding or fashioning",
      "answer": "formative"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a thrusting forward movement  ",
      "answer": "lunge"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking pretension or affectation",
      "answer": "unpretentious"
    },
    {
      "question": "expressing or manifesting disapproval  ",
      "answer": "disapproving"
    },
    {
      "question": "a set sequence of steps, part of larger computer program  ",
      "answer": "routine"
    },
    {
      "question": "add to the end  ",
      "answer": "subjoin"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of endorsing",
      "answer": "endorsement"
    },
    {
      "question": "not genuine or real",
      "answer": "fake"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a glance) sidelong and slyly lascivious",
      "answer": "leering"
    },
    {
      "question": "act in order to achieve a certain goal",
      "answer": "maneuver"
    },
    {
      "question": "the wool of the Kashmir goat  ",
      "answer": "cashmere"
    },
    {
      "question": "lawfulness by virtue of being authorized or in accordance with law  ",
      "answer": "legitimacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "intellectual depth",
      "answer": "profundity"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who settles on land without right or title  ",
      "answer": "squatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "tropical American tree producing cacao beans  ",
      "answer": "cacao"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Jungian psychology) the inner self (not the external persona) that is in touch with the unconscious  ",
      "answer": "anima"
    },
    {
      "question": "a political theory favoring unlimited authority by a single individual  ",
      "answer": "autocracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the cutting of or into body tissues or organs (especially by a surgeon as part of an operation)  ",
      "answer": "incision"
    },
    {
      "question": "of relatively low or level country  ",
      "answer": "lowland"
    },
    {
      "question": "according to tradition",
      "answer": "traditionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being advisable",
      "answer": "advisability"
    },
    {
      "question": "a figure of a man used as a supporting column  ",
      "answer": "atlas"
    },
    {
      "question": "determined by geography",
      "answer": "geographic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a movable top or cover (hinged or separate) for closing the opening at the top of a box, chest, jar, pan, etc.",
      "answer": "lid"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of marshaling and organizing and making ready for use or action",
      "answer": "mobilization"
    },
    {
      "question": "rendered motionless for lack of wind  ",
      "answer": "becalmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "infect with a canker  ",
      "answer": "canker"
    },
    {
      "question": "secret agreement  ",
      "answer": "collusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stock or supply of foods  ",
      "answer": "commissariat"
    },
    {
      "question": "crouch or curl up",
      "answer": "huddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of pouring a liquid offering (especially wine) as a religious ceremony  ",
      "answer": "libation"
    },
    {
      "question": "overfull as with blood  ",
      "answer": "congested"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of conduct",
      "answer": "debasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "give up, such as power, as of monarchs and emperors, or duties and obligations",
      "answer": "abdicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property possessed by a line or surface that is curved and not angular  ",
      "answer": "roundness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a barge carrying bulk materials in an open hold  ",
      "answer": "scow"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a travesty of  ",
      "answer": "travesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "position on a scale in relation to others in a sport  ",
      "answer": "ranking"
    },
    {
      "question": "enter into someone's consciousness",
      "answer": "register"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the state of development between puberty and maturity",
      "answer": "adolescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman benefactor  ",
      "answer": "benefactress"
    },
    {
      "question": "failing in what duty requires",
      "answer": "derelict"
    },
    {
      "question": "an invasion or hostile attack  ",
      "answer": "inroad"
    },
    {
      "question": "find the solution to (a problem or question) or understand the meaning of",
      "answer": "solve"
    },
    {
      "question": "lost temporarily",
      "answer": "mislaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various small mouselike rodents of the family Cricetidae (especially of genus Microtus) having a stout short-tailed body and inconspicuous ears and inhabiting fields or meadows  ",
      "answer": "vole"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a moderate purple color  ",
      "answer": "amethyst"
    },
    {
      "question": "matching point for point",
      "answer": "coincident"
    },
    {
      "question": "the entire scale of musical notes  ",
      "answer": "gamut"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a harmless manner",
      "answer": "harmlessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ritual recitation of words or sounds believed to have a magical effect  ",
      "answer": "incantation"
    },
    {
      "question": "holds a license (degree) from a (European) university  ",
      "answer": "licentiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a substantial amount",
      "answer": "chunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "affording reasonable grounds for belief or acceptance",
      "answer": "presumptive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a scientist trained in psychology  ",
      "answer": "psychologist"
    },
    {
      "question": "eject from the premises",
      "answer": "bounce"
    },
    {
      "question": " being born or beginning",
      "answer": "nascent"
    },
    {
      "question": "not having a coat of paint or badly in need of a fresh coat",
      "answer": "unpainted"
    },
    {
      "question": "a political orientation of a people or a government to maintain a strong military force and to be prepared to use it aggressively to defend or promote national interests  ",
      "answer": "militarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "large sweet fleshy tropical fruit with a terminal tuft of stiff leaves",
      "answer": "pineapple"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of making broader",
      "answer": "broadening"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who has or gives or receives a part or a share  ",
      "answer": "partaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "a barrister or solicitor who serves as part-time judge in towns or boroughs  ",
      "answer": "recorder"
    },
    {
      "question": "whip with or as if with a wire whisk",
      "answer": "whisk"
    },
    {
      "question": "provided with a floor  ",
      "answer": "floored"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the scientific study of speech sounds",
      "answer": "phonetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an organism (person or animal) that sits  ",
      "answer": "sitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "statements affirming or denying certain matters of fact that you are prepared to prove  ",
      "answer": "allegation"
    },
    {
      "question": "an illegal pitching motion while runners are on base  ",
      "answer": "balk"
    },
    {
      "question": "an extension at the end and at right angles to the main building  ",
      "answer": "ell"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling sculpture",
      "answer": "modeled"
    },
    {
      "question": "the position of professor",
      "answer": "professorship"
    },
    {
      "question": "an elaborate analytical or explanatory essay or discussion  ",
      "answer": "disquisition"
    },
    {
      "question": "make chemically neutral",
      "answer": "neutralize"
    },
    {
      "question": "(theology) being determined in advance",
      "answer": "predestination"
    },
    {
      "question": "deductive reasoning in which a conclusion is derived from two premises  ",
      "answer": "syllogism"
    },
    {
      "question": "without due formalities",
      "answer": "unceremonious"
    },
    {
      "question": "screw thread on a gear with the teeth of a worm wheel or rack  ",
      "answer": "worm"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of soil) soft and watery",
      "answer": "boggy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a headlike protuberance on an organ or structure",
      "answer": "caput"
    },
    {
      "question": "look down on with disdain",
      "answer": "contemn"
    },
    {
      "question": "the work of using heat to smooth washed clothes in order to remove any wrinkles  ",
      "answer": "ironing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the political orientation of those who hold that a republic is the best form of government  ",
      "answer": "republicanism"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a righteous manner",
      "answer": "righteously"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female tiger  ",
      "answer": "tigress"
    },
    {
      "question": "the highest level or degree attainable",
      "answer": "acme"
    },
    {
      "question": "morally obligatory",
      "answer": "bounden"
    },
    {
      "question": "apparent validity  ",
      "answer": "plausibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "having characteristics associated with women and considered undesirable in men",
      "answer": "womanish"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being rude and impertinent",
      "answer": "crust"
    },
    {
      "question": "beautiful carriage  ",
      "answer": "gracefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "narcotic consisting of an alcohol solution of opium or any preparation in which opium is the main ingredient  ",
      "answer": "laudanum"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a monotonous manner",
      "answer": "monotonously"
    },
    {
      "question": "enclose with a dike",
      "answer": "dike"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a region of the United States generally including the New England states",
      "answer": "northeastern"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a wrathful manner",
      "answer": "wrathfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing firm determination or purpose",
      "answer": "resolutely"
    },
    {
      "question": "coils of worsted yarn  ",
      "answer": "skein"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ability to change (or be changed) to fit changed circumstances  ",
      "answer": "adaptability"
    },
    {
      "question": "process fast and efficiently",
      "answer": "expedite"
    },
    {
      "question": "be at or take the helm of",
      "answer": "helm"
    },
    {
      "question": "idyllically calm and peaceful",
      "answer": "halcyon"
    },
    {
      "question": "take part in a riot",
      "answer": "riot"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) the intentional destruction of a document or an alteration of it that destroys its value as evidence  ",
      "answer": "spoliation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trail left by a person or an animal",
      "answer": "spoor"
    },
    {
      "question": "laugh loudly and harshly  ",
      "answer": "bray"
    },
    {
      "question": "hamper the action or progress of",
      "answer": "hobble"
    },
    {
      "question": "not prominent or readily noticeable",
      "answer": "inconspicuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "dance a quick dance with leaping and kicking motions  ",
      "answer": "jig"
    },
    {
      "question": "small slender fish (to 8 inches) with body covered by bony plates",
      "answer": "poacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "living or growing above the timber line",
      "answer": "alpine"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various rough thorny shrubs or vines  ",
      "answer": "bramble"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of singing popular songs in a sentimental manner  ",
      "answer": "crooning"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activity of representing something by a special system of marks or characters  ",
      "answer": "notation"
    },
    {
      "question": "rickettsial disease transmitted by body lice and characterized by skin rash and high fever  ",
      "answer": "typhus"
    },
    {
      "question": "abounding with or resembling weeds",
      "answer": "weedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "generator consisting of a coil (the armature) that rotates between the poles of an electromagnet (the field magnet) causing a current to flow in the armature  ",
      "answer": "dynamo"
    },
    {
      "question": "a critical study (as of a writer's work)  ",
      "answer": "examen"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered with beads of liquid",
      "answer": "beaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long cigar with blunt ends  ",
      "answer": "corona"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who dispenses  ",
      "answer": "dispenser"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman who is engaged to be married  ",
      "answer": "fiancee"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a musical manner",
      "answer": "musically"
    },
    {
      "question": "(genetics) a segment of DNA that is involved in producing a polypeptide chain",
      "answer": "gene"
    },
    {
      "question": "perform a stunt or stunts  ",
      "answer": "stunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "small carnivorous mammal with short legs and elongated body and neck  ",
      "answer": "weasel"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or determined by sociology",
      "answer": "sociological"
    },
    {
      "question": "extreme hostility",
      "answer": "virulence"
    },
    {
      "question": "a complaint uttered in a plaintive whining way  ",
      "answer": "whimper"
    },
    {
      "question": "tenure by which land is held in fee simple or for life  ",
      "answer": "freehold"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of mastering or subordinating someone  ",
      "answer": "mastery"
    },
    {
      "question": "firearm that is a double-barreled smoothbore shoulder weapon for firing shot at short ranges  ",
      "answer": "shotgun"
    },
    {
      "question": "a confident assertive person who acts as instigator  ",
      "answer": "aggressor"
    },
    {
      "question": "no longer sufficient",
      "answer": "depleted"
    },
    {
      "question": "care for one's external appearance",
      "answer": "groom"
    },
    {
      "question": "a common white or colorless mineral (hydrated calcium sulphate) used to make cements and plasters (especially plaster of Paris)  ",
      "answer": "gypsum"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large cask especially one holding 63 gals  ",
      "answer": "hogshead"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or dealing with philology  ",
      "answer": "philological"
    },
    {
      "question": "skill in sailing  ",
      "answer": "seamanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "a crane for moving material with dispatch as in loading and unloading ships  ",
      "answer": "transporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a cadaver or corpse",
      "answer": "cadaverous"
    },
    {
      "question": "musteline mammal of northern Eurasia  ",
      "answer": "glutton"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a feeling of home",
      "answer": "homelike"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or inside the intestines",
      "answer": "intestinal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of ending something",
      "answer": "termination"
    },
    {
      "question": "abnormally distended especially by fluids or gas",
      "answer": "puffy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person disposed to take a favorable view of things  ",
      "answer": "optimist"
    },
    {
      "question": "make impure",
      "answer": "pollute"
    },
    {
      "question": "suggestive of a thyroid disorder",
      "answer": "thyroid"
    },
    {
      "question": "attach a suffix to",
      "answer": "suffix"
    },
    {
      "question": "not cut",
      "answer": "uncut"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to an equinox (when the lengths of night and day are equal)  ",
      "answer": "equinoctial"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to walls",
      "answer": "mural"
    },
    {
      "question": "seating on the main floor between the orchestra and the parquet circle  ",
      "answer": "parquet"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking a sense of responsibility  ",
      "answer": "unreliable"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an expectant manner",
      "answer": "expectantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "protesting  ",
      "answer": "protestant"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the manner of something that has become a byword",
      "answer": "proverbially"
    },
    {
      "question": "an Italian courtesy title for an unmarried woman",
      "answer": "signorina"
    },
    {
      "question": "large metal container in which coal or charcoal is burned",
      "answer": "brazier"
    },
    {
      "question": "detailed critical analysis or examination one part at a time (as of a literary work)  ",
      "answer": "dissection"
    },
    {
      "question": "markedly effective as if by emotional pressure",
      "answer": "impelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "manual stimulation of the genital organs (of yourself or another) for sexual pleasure  ",
      "answer": "masturbation"
    },
    {
      "question": "worthless or oversimplified ideas  ",
      "answer": "pap"
    },
    {
      "question": "a slight or superficial understanding of a subject  ",
      "answer": "smattering"
    },
    {
      "question": "unwelcome and unwanted",
      "answer": "uninvited"
    },
    {
      "question": "fishing with a hook and line (and usually a pole)  ",
      "answer": "angling"
    },
    {
      "question": "acute abdominal pain (especially in infants)  ",
      "answer": "colic"
    },
    {
      "question": "toward the bottom of a hill",
      "answer": "downhill"
    },
    {
      "question": "an Italian title of respect for a man",
      "answer": "signore"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of describing distinctive characteristics or essential features",
      "answer": "characterization"
    },
    {
      "question": "extreme mental retardation  ",
      "answer": "idiocy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disrespectful act  ",
      "answer": "irreverence"
    },
    {
      "question": "used incorrectly or carelessly or for an improper purpose",
      "answer": "misused"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musical composition for four performers  ",
      "answer": "quartet"
    },
    {
      "question": "emotionally upset",
      "answer": "unstrung"
    },
    {
      "question": "habitually disposed to disobedience and opposition  ",
      "answer": "froward"
    },
    {
      "question": "reduce (a sail) by taking in a reef  ",
      "answer": "reef"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from physical or moral spots or stains",
      "answer": "unblemished"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musician who is a consummate master of technique and artistry  ",
      "answer": "virtuoso"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of acting or a stage performance",
      "answer": "histrionic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sudden outburst of cheers",
      "answer": "salvo"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman chaperon  ",
      "answer": "duenna"
    },
    {
      "question": "the office of admiral  ",
      "answer": "admiralty"
    },
    {
      "question": "a horse-drawn carriage having four wheels",
      "answer": "barouche"
    },
    {
      "question": "sew together loosely, with large stitches",
      "answer": "baste"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a decent and morally reputable manner",
      "answer": "respectably"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of being bent or deflected  ",
      "answer": "deflection"
    },
    {
      "question": "a protective headgear made of hard material to resist blows  ",
      "answer": "helmet"
    },
    {
      "question": "like the discordant ringing of nonmusical metallic objects striking together",
      "answer": "jangling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a man who takes advantage of women  ",
      "answer": "seducer"
    },
    {
      "question": "become coke",
      "answer": "coke"
    },
    {
      "question": "elevated open grassland in southern Africa  ",
      "answer": "veld"
    },
    {
      "question": "depression resulting from an undermining of your morale  ",
      "answer": "demoralization"
    },
    {
      "question": "the body of enfranchised citizens",
      "answer": "electorate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a complete and impressive array  ",
      "answer": "panoply"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to the use of or having the nature of an interrogation  ",
      "answer": "interrogative"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a characteristic sound, of a horse  ",
      "answer": "neigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "beat through cleverness and wit",
      "answer": "outwit"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mutual promise of a couple not to date anyone else",
      "answer": "pinning"
    },
    {
      "question": "a detailed and documented treatise on a particular subject  ",
      "answer": "monograph"
    },
    {
      "question": "the internal supporting structure that gives an artifact its shape",
      "answer": "skeleton"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to lose courage",
      "answer": "daunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) the unlawful act of capturing and carrying away a person against their will and holding them in false imprisonment  ",
      "answer": "kidnapping"
    },
    {
      "question": "(pathology) a firm abnormal elevated blemish on the skin",
      "answer": "wart"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of showing affection  ",
      "answer": "endearment"
    },
    {
      "question": "give out (breath or an odor)",
      "answer": "exhale"
    },
    {
      "question": "a supplement to a will",
      "answer": "codicil"
    },
    {
      "question": "immediately after this",
      "answer": "hereupon"
    },
    {
      "question": "sing and play for somebody",
      "answer": "serenade"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert to compost",
      "answer": "compost"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the back and shoulders rounded",
      "answer": "hunched"
    },
    {
      "question": "proceed or issue forth, as from a source",
      "answer": "emanate"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inaccurate manner",
      "answer": "incorrectly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stately piece of music composed for dancing the minuet",
      "answer": "minuet"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who agitates",
      "answer": "agitator"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of pairing a male and female for reproductive purposes",
      "answer": "coupling"
    },
    {
      "question": "of an optical system (e.g. eye or opera glasses) adjusted to produce a clear image  ",
      "answer": "focused"
    },
    {
      "question": "a building occupied by a state legislature  ",
      "answer": "capitol"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of Cockneys or their dialect",
      "answer": "cockney"
    },
    {
      "question": "speak with a lisp  ",
      "answer": "lisp"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of joining together as one",
      "answer": "merging"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring at or dependent on a particular season",
      "answer": "seasonal"
    },
    {
      "question": "tie with a tether",
      "answer": "tether"
    },
    {
      "question": "a plant where beer is brewed by fermentation  ",
      "answer": "brewery"
    },
    {
      "question": "(ancient Rome) a professional combatant or a captive who entertained the public by engaging in mortal combat  ",
      "answer": "gladiator"
    },
    {
      "question": "made grainy or formed into granules",
      "answer": "granulated"
    },
    {
      "question": "carelessly failing to exercise proper caution",
      "answer": "incautious"
    },
    {
      "question": "a somewhat flat reddish-orange loose skinned citrus of China  ",
      "answer": "mandarin"
    },
    {
      "question": "part of the perianth that is usually brightly colored  ",
      "answer": "petal"
    },
    {
      "question": "not carefully reworked or perfected or made smooth by polishing",
      "answer": "unpolished"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large fleet  ",
      "answer": "armada"
    },
    {
      "question": "the enclosing frame around a door or window opening",
      "answer": "casing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a political theory favoring collectivism in a classless society  ",
      "answer": "communism"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a sophisticated charm",
      "answer": "debonair"
    },
    {
      "question": "to an inconceivable degree",
      "answer": "inconceivably"
    },
    {
      "question": "befitting a woman of good breeding",
      "answer": "ladylike"
    },
    {
      "question": "without profit or reward",
      "answer": "profitless"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being without practical use  ",
      "answer": "worthlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from obscurity and easy to understand",
      "answer": "clarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "brought into equipoise by means of a weight or force that offsets another  ",
      "answer": "counterbalanced"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing frivolous or superficial interest",
      "answer": "dilettante"
    },
    {
      "question": "change into a vapor",
      "answer": "evaporate"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a metaphorical manner",
      "answer": "metaphorically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state or territory partly controlled by (but not a possession of) a stronger state but autonomous in internal affairs",
      "answer": "protectorate"
    },
    {
      "question": "dressed in a uniform",
      "answer": "uniformed"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing unselfish concern for the welfare of others  ",
      "answer": "altruistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a plant with a weak stem that derives support from climbing, twining, or creeping along a surface  ",
      "answer": "vine"
    },
    {
      "question": "unaged colorless liquor originating in Russia  ",
      "answer": "vodka"
    },
    {
      "question": "dress with a corset  ",
      "answer": "corset"
    },
    {
      "question": "a signal to get up in the morning",
      "answer": "reveille"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt fowl in the forest  ",
      "answer": "fowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing little if any change",
      "answer": "static"
    },
    {
      "question": "early testing stage of a software or hardware product",
      "answer": "alpha"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ability to read and write  ",
      "answer": "literacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a morbid manner or to a morbid degree",
      "answer": "morbidly"
    },
    {
      "question": "hypothetical remedy for all ills or diseases",
      "answer": "panacea"
    },
    {
      "question": "communicating at a distance by electric transmission over wire  ",
      "answer": "telegraphy"
    },
    {
      "question": "imprisonment (especially for a long time)  ",
      "answer": "durance"
    },
    {
      "question": "the person who steers a ship  ",
      "answer": "helmsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a hysterical manner",
      "answer": "hysterically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who expects the worst  ",
      "answer": "pessimist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musical composition of 3 or 4 movements of contrasting forms  ",
      "answer": "sonata"
    },
    {
      "question": "a silky-coated sheepdog with a long ruff and long narrow head developed in Scotland  ",
      "answer": "collie"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lack of politeness",
      "answer": "discourtesy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of emerging  ",
      "answer": "emergence"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of not being ripe  ",
      "answer": "greenness"
    },
    {
      "question": "have a bowel movement",
      "answer": "stool"
    },
    {
      "question": "not subject to a condition",
      "answer": "unconditionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "something won (especially money)  ",
      "answer": "winnings"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several small active brown birds of the northern hemisphere with short upright tails",
      "answer": "wren"
    },
    {
      "question": "grain ground into flour  ",
      "answer": "buckwheat"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a quizzical and questioning manner",
      "answer": "questioningly"
    },
    {
      "question": "subject to bitter verbal abuse  ",
      "answer": "vitriol"
    },
    {
      "question": "one of two basic subdivisions of a tribe  ",
      "answer": "moiety"
    },
    {
      "question": "(usually followed by `to') not affected by a given influence",
      "answer": "immune"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of extreme poverty or destitution",
      "answer": "indigence"
    },
    {
      "question": "calculated to please or gain favor",
      "answer": "ingratiating"
    },
    {
      "question": "visible",
      "answer": "ocular"
    },
    {
      "question": "a float supporting a seaplane  ",
      "answer": "pontoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "powdery starch from certain sago palms",
      "answer": "sago"
    },
    {
      "question": "tenants of an estate considered as a group  ",
      "answer": "tenantry"
    },
    {
      "question": "a concluding action  ",
      "answer": "completion"
    }
  ]
}